Sem Plaatsman

My name is Sem Plaatsman, a Computer Science student at Inholland University of Applied Sciences in Haarlem. Over the past four years, I have been able to utilize my curiosity and passion for problem-solving in various projects using tools such as .NET, Java, GitHub, AI, and React. For example, I helped develop an AI speech recognition system for TNO, and in the field, an SSO system. My ambition is to further develop my skills in DevOps and cloud (Azure).

CONTACT INFORMATION

Website:semplaatsman.nlEmail:hello@semplaatsman.nlGitHub:github.com/SemPlaatsmanLinkedIn:linkedin.com/in/sem-plaatsman

WORK EXPERIENCE

S.P. Abonneeservice 03/2024 - present

Automation Employee

Haarlem, Netherlands

 Worked on an SSO system and an AI model that tries to predict when a customer will cancel. This AI model is being integrated into the existing retention modules.

S.P. Abonneeservice 09/2023 – 01/2024

Development Intern

Haarlem, Netherlands

- Developed a JWT-authenticated PWA for mobile access to customer statistics. Used as a sales argument for new customers, among other things.
- Worked closely with management and IT team. Analyzed requirements and technically translated them for stakeholders.
- Gained experience with React, ASP.NET, JWT, TypeScript, SCSS, and MySQL, among others.

EDUCATION

Inholland University of Applied Sciences

09/2021 - present

Informatica full-time | Bachelor

Haarlem, Netherlands

- In year 2, I helped first-year students with C# programming (credit point).
- As project leader, successfully directed and completed decision-making regarding system design and technical choices.
- Strong in setting up and modeling software architectures; achieved a 10 for both Cloud Databases and Functional Modeling, where developing architectures was central. Completed first-year diploma (propedeuse) in the first year.

OSG De Hogeberg

09/2015 - 07/2021

Texel, Netherlands

- High school | HAVO
- Thesis project about AI.
- Became interested in programming during a Python project in HAVO 4.

SKILLS & INTERESTS

- **Soft skills:** Solution-oriented, perseverance, helpful, eager to learn.
- Hard skills: OOP, Modeling, GitHub, Web, AI, Software Design Patterns, DevOps, Azure.
- **Interesses:** Automation, microprocessors, containerization, gym, and bouldering.